<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>jasmineke on Jasmine Ke</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in jasmineke on Jasmine Ke</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:20:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Next Steps!</title><link>/posts/template/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 19:20:44 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/template/</guid><description>I want to:
add a loading screen between pages have a side &amp;ldquo;legend&amp;rdquo; on each of the case-study and blog pages talk about how this site was created with yifei from scratch! home-made goodness :)</description></item><item><title>Biztech Webapp</title><link>/works/biztech-webapp/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/works/biztech-webapp/</guid><description>Biztech Webapp Event Form For 150&amp;#43; members registering for events
Why did we make this app? Our team at Biztech was organizing events using google forms, spreadsheets, Hopin.to, etc. and we noticed that there was an opportunity to make this process less cluttered and more efficient. Our developer team jumped on this opportunity, and over the course of months, we worked together to create a fully-realized in-house webform.</description></item><item><title>blueprint</title><link>/works/blueprint/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/works/blueprint/</guid><description>Hi! 👋🏻 Thanks for dropping by, this case study is still a work in progress&amp;hellip; meanwhile here are some other works!</description></item><item><title>Food Baby</title><link>/works/food-baby/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/works/food-baby/</guid><description>Food Baby 1st Place Google Cloud Award @ cmd-f
Why did we make this app? For the to-be-moms around the world, sometimes knowing what is healthy for their baby isn&amp;rsquo;t always clear. Although some foods and drinks like alcohol are easier to identify as harmful, there are also more obscure foods like cheese and chips that are less obvious and sometimes harmful in certain amounts.
We thought of the pregnant women that go to get groceries, sometimes unsure about which foods to get.</description></item></channel></rss>